[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played the character of Jill Valentine in Resident Evil: Apocalypse?", "correct_answer": "Sienna Guillory", "incorrect_answers": ["Terri Morales", "Ashanti", "Michelle Rodriguez"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the director of the movie 48 Hrs.?", "correct_answer": "Walter Hill", "incorrect_answers": ["Ron Howard", "Martin Scorcese", "Henry Winkler"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of body modification is the artificial cranial deformation, in which a part of the body is reshaped by applying force?", "correct_answer": "Deformation of the skull", "incorrect_answers": ["Deformation of the fingers", "Deformation of the ribs", "Deformation of the toes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played Beau as a 12 -year-old in Beau Geste?", "correct_answer": "Donald OConnor", "incorrect_answers": ["Robert Mitchum", "Humphrey Bogart", "James Dean"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is the largest species of penguins?", "correct_answer": "Emperor Penguin", "incorrect_answers": ["King Penguin", "Giant Penguin", "Royal Penguin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If you stick bubble gum in your hair, you can remove it with a small amount of this substance.", "correct_answer": "Peanut butter", "incorrect_answers": ["Water", "Flour", "Alcohol"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In a tropical cyclone, this area is characterized with the strongest winds, the tallest clouds, and the heaviest rain.", "correct_answer": "Eyewall", "incorrect_answers": ["Eye", "Warm core", "Outflow"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "These are often used as weather indicators. Before the weather gets dry, they open up. If it will be wet, they return to their normal shape.", "correct_answer": "Pine cones", "incorrect_answers": ["Dandelions", "Pea pods", "Willow sprigs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "After three unsuccessful runs, this socialist was elected President in 1970.", "correct_answer": "Salvador Allende", "incorrect_answers": ["Miquel Noriega", "Dmitri Kerensky", "Ivan Beria"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Jack Napier/The Jokers right-hand man throughout the movie Batman?", "correct_answer": "Bob", "incorrect_answers": ["John", "Chad", "Tom"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to the August 2008 issue of Travel  Leisure, what is the scariest road in the world?", "correct_answer": "N. Yungas Road, Bolivia", "incorrect_answers": ["Karakoram Hwy., Pakistan to China", "Guoliang Tunnel Road, China", "Halsena Hwy., Luzon, Philippines"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Kansas is entirely in the Central time zone.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]